tomferry.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy

Ferry International, LLC dba Tom Ferry, provides coaching and training strategies to professionals in the real estate industry.

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Tom Ferry (sometimes referred to as TF, Ferry International) website and the HUB and various related services (together referred to as the “sites”). Tom Ferry is referred to as “us” or “we, and is committed to protecting your privacy online.

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Sites’ Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our sites, you agree to be bound by all of the sites’ terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use these sites.

Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of these sites:

  1. What information do we collect from you?
  2. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?
  3. With whom do we share your information?
  4. How can you update, correct or delete your Personally Identifiable Information?
  5. What are your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?
  6. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
  7. Do we use “cookies”?
  8. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third party sites accessible from our sites?
  9. What else should you know about your privacy online?
  10. What about video calling sessions?
  11. Is any of your information available to other users?
  12. What if you have any other questions or concerns?

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by means including, but not limited to issuing an e-mail to the e-mail address listed by registered users and/or posting the revised Policy on this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review these sites and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the sites after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.  

### 1\. What information do we collect from you?

In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our sites.

Personally, Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on these sites, such as registering as a member, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the sites, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our sites in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site’s Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. An URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (“TCP/IP”) network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.

### 2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you:  
(a) register as a member of any of our sites and/or register your e-mail address with us;  
(b) enter sweepstakes or contests sponsored by us or one of our partners;  
(c) sign up for special offers from selected third parties  
(d) send e-mail messages, submit forms or transmit other information by telephone or letter;  
(e) track your listings or progress; or  
(f) submit your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our sites.

We may also collect information from you at other points on our sites that state that such information is being collected.

In addition, we may also collect, or our third-party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. This information is ultimately stored in the form of store categories, and, in some cases, specific URLs. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our sites and to gather demographic information. Our third-party ad servers will also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our sites.

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our services to you, as required by our agreements with you. We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our sites, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, directly market to you, statistically analyze sites use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our sites’ content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Sites Terms of Use, Sales Terms and Conditions, and this Private Policy.

### 2.1 European Specific Provisions

With effect from 25 May 2018, Tom Ferry International will Process Personal Data in accordance with the GDPR requirements directly applicable to Tom Ferry International’s provisioning of the Services. 2.1.1 Data Protection Impact Assessment. Upon Customer’s request, Tom Ferry International shall provide Customer with reasonable cooperation and assistance needed to fulfill Customer’s obligation under the GDPR to carry out a data protection impact assessment related to Customer’s use of the Services, to the extent Customer does not otherwise have access to the relevant information, and to the extent such information is available to Tom Ferry International. Tom Ferry International shall provide reasonable assistance to Customer in the cooperation or prior consultation with the Supervisory Authority, to the extent required under the GDPR.

### 3\. With whom do we share your information?

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others outside of the network. We do provide some of our services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, therefore, for example, upon your election (i.e. upon your checking a box), certain information is provided during transactions on our eCommerce store. We and our service partners use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver their services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on these sites; release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered; and provide order information to third-parties that help us provide customer service.  
We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who is violating our Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with other of the sites’ users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers’ sales, traffic patterns, and related sites information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

We may share reports with third parties based on aggregated data of our Members (“Aggregated Member Data”). Aggregated Member Data does not include any personally identifiable information. For example, these reports will not include your personal or organization name. Information about Members is aggregated for the purposes of determining successful event benchmarks and other similar activities.

There are certain areas of our sites wherein you input information with the obvious purpose to share or disclose that information. Therefore, you are advised to exercise discretion in inputting your information in those areas of the sites.

If you are purchasing a product, we may request payment information to complete the transaction, as well as your mailing address or other contact information to ensure authentication and proper delivery. We use industry-standard secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. We do not sell or rent your personal financial information. When you engage in an eCommerce transaction on our sites using a credit card, your credit card information, including the number and expiration date and your billing address, is passed onto the merchant with whom the transaction was placed; only we and the merchant with whom you placed the order has access to your credit card information. Your credit card information is stored with each order in our system just long enough to fully process your transaction. After the transaction has completed, your credit card information is removed from our system for security reasons. You may decline to provide credit card information and any other information at our site at any time. If you should choose to withhold requested information; however, we may not be able to provide you with the full spectrum of our services.

### 4\. How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information in your account online at any time by linking to your account in accordance with instructions posted elsewhere on these sites. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by emailing us at [cs@tomferry.com.](mailto:cs@tomferry.com.)  _Please be advised that updating or removing your information as to one of our sites does not automatically update or remove your information as to any other of our sites. Your information must be updated or removed from each site, individually._

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.  
We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on these sites. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups.

### 5\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?

We may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services. In addition, if you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us and our partners, we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only we (or agents working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. At any time, you can easily edit your account information to no longer receive such offers and mailings or inform us by contacting us at [cs@tomferry.com.](mailto:cs@tomferry.com.) Please note that editing your account information as to one of our sites does not automatically edit your account information as to any other of our sites. Your information must be edited on each site, individually.

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our sites may not work properly in your case.

### 6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?

At our sites you can be assured that your Personally Identifiable Information is maintained consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all Personally Identifiable Information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. Your Personally Identifiable Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Personally Identifiable Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to via password. We protect your Personally Identifiable Information through a firewall and encryption and thereby prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to us.

Personal information that you provide that is not Personally Identifiable Information also resides on a secure server and is only accessible via password. Since this information is not accessible from outside you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through these sites cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third-party.

### 7\. Do we use “cookies”?

When you use our sites, we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our sites. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our sites. A cookie cannot read data from your hard drive or cookie files created by other websites. We use cookies to “time-out” your session if it is idle for a long period of time. The cookies make your use of the sites easier, make the sites run more smoothly and help us to maintain secure sites. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our sites may not work properly in that case.

Browser manufacturers provide help pages relating to cookie management in their products. Please see below for more information.

For other browsers, please consult the documentation that your browser manufacturer provides.  
We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on The HUB. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your device. We will not provide any third-party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information or information about your purchases. We and our third-party ad server will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our sites in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them.

### 8\. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third-party sites accessible from our sites?

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our sites have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each sites’ privacy policies. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies which place advertising on our sites may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

### 9\. What else should you know about your privacy online?

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use these sites. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 18 years of age.

### 10\. What about video calling sessions?

As a Coaching Client of Ferry International, LLC, you have the option of having your coaching sessions recorded (image and voice), via the Company’s Video Coaching Service inside The HUB. This permits you to conduct your sessions “face to face” and to review your sessions to ensure that you can recall advice, practice tips or goals discussed in your Coaching session. On occasion, the Company may also review your session for purposes including, without limitation, quality control. You are not required to record any of your sessions. However, once recorded they become and remain the property of the Company. Your use of the Video Coaching Service inside The HUB indicates your agreement to these provisions. In the event you disagree with this policy, and wish to opt out, uncheck the box listed around this message in The HUB and you are free to conduct your sessions via video, without being recorded.

### 11\. Is any of your information available to other users?

You should also be aware that there are certain areas of our sites where by entering certain information, it is available to the other registered members of the site to view. Any information disclosed by you in these areas of the site is voluntary on your part. You are advised to use discretion. Information you voluntarily disclose in those areas of the site are beyond our control and our privacy assurance does not apply to such information. Any submissions are accessible to all other members of the site. If you do not want such information to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions.

### 12\. What if you have any other questions or concerns?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of these sites, or your dealings with these sites, please contact us by emailing cs@tomferry.com Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer.

CONCLUSION: Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.
